原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨  VioletCheng
翻译     AlgerDestiny  五天  二糯米  不见大星
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     西·查
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
《辛普森一家》
第31季第10集
自己会飞的雪橇
圣诞节前五周
现在有足够时间订圣诞礼物了
And now to order my Christmas gifts with plenty of time.
背带
几天之后
UPS快递
UPS快递追踪说我的包裹刚到
UPS tracking says my packages just arrived.
我只要往下看就是
All I have to do is look down.
寄给莱尼·莱昂纳德
谁会干这种事  谁
Who could've done this? Who?
*叮咚  你好呀*
*Ding-donong, merrily on hi*
*天堂的铃声灵灵灵*
*In heaven the bells are ringing*
颜料
*叮咚  巴仔要死啦*
*Ding-dong, Bart is gonna die*
*我吊着他的小脖子*
*His little neck I'm stringing.*
死吧  巴仔去死
需要点金箔
Needs tinsel
衬托巴仔眼神中的恐惧
to reflect the horror in Bart's eyes.
金箔
有客人  来啦
Oh, a visitor. Coming.
你好  这儿有没有孤单的灯塔看守人被遗忘了
Ahoy! Are there any lonely lighthouse keepers abaft here?
你好  卡珊德拉
Oh, hello, Cassandra.
惊喜哦  我给你做了松饼
Surprise! I made you muffins.
想知道一个秘密吗
You want to know a secret?
我用了两块黄油
I used two sticks of butter.
你有没有黑暗深藏的秘密呢
Do you have any deep dark secrets?
爱
恨
春田监狱
圣诞快乐  神父
Merry Christmas, Father!
别惹事儿
Stay out of trouble.
木有  没有秘密
Nope. No secrets.
你想过孩子们吗
So, have you ever thought about children?
想我  想我  现在你得亲亲我
Missed me! Missed me! Now you gotta kiss me!
不好意思
Oh, if you'll excuse me,
我的平衡环需要上鲸油
my gimbals need a good whale oiling.
你可能还会有别的访客
you might get some other visitors.
我今天在镇上提到你了
I mentioned you in town today.
你跟人们说起我了  你说了什么  什么
You told people about me? What did you tell them?! What?!
我说你有善良的眼睛  优美的嗓音
That you had kind eyes, a beautiful voice,
还是单身贵族
and no wedding ring.
他在那儿呢
There he is!
我真是愚蠢  对一个
I was a fool to let my guard down with a woman
有朝海的菲涅尔透镜的女人放下了戒备
who runs a seaward-aiming Fresnel lens!
我从地狱里向你们发来死亡问候
From hell's heart I stab at thee!
天哪  听听这如蜜一般的男中音
Oh, my God. Just listen to that mellifluous baritone.
他太适合这个角色了
He's perfect for the role.
角色  角色
Role? Role?
你要提供我一份表演工作
You're offering me an acting job?
没错  在一个小公园扮演圣诞老人
Yes! It's to play Santa Claus at a small amusement park.
管他呢  是领衔主演  我上
Oh, what the hell. It is the lead. I'm in!
有晚餐了
Dinner is served.
圣诞节前一周
圣诞树
科斯汀顿商场
看看你狗牌上写了啥
Hey, let's see what's on your tag.
嗅尸犬
"Cadaver-sniffing dog"?!
这也是个我没能得到的工作
Ah, that's another job I didn't get.
UPS快递
不见了  我修理门廊的工具箱没了
It's gone. My porch repair kit is gone!
帮帮忙吧
A little help!
又一个失败的手工
Another crafts project gone out of hand?
-对  -如果你明天不忙
- Yes. - If you're not tied up tomorrow,
我请一天假
I took the day off from work.
我想我们可以看一部R级电影
I was thinking we could watch an R-rated movie.
一部多利萝玛餐厅里性感肋排的故事
Finally, the sexy story of Tony Roma's ribs.
《罗马》
但是我答应了孩子们明天带他们去玩
But tomorrow I promised the kids I'd take them out of school.
可以当成家庭日
It can be our family day.
呵呵
Yawn.
我们可以去圣诞老人村
We'll go to Santa's Village.
我讨厌那地方  圣诞节那里人太多了
Oh, I hate that place. It's so crowded at Christmas.
那个巨型糖果拐杖也不是真的
And the giant candy canes are not real.
但是通了电
But they are electrified!
我们就是要带着孩子们去
Well, we're going and taking the kids.
为什么那个不是我呢
Why couldn't that be me?
侯默
Homer!
距圣诞老人村还有32英里
*鲨鱼宝宝  嘟嘟嘟嘟*
*Baby shark, doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo*
天哪  我实在是听够了
Oh, God, I'm so sick of this.
*鲨鱼宝宝*
*Baby shark,*
一直唱啊唱
Thing just keeps going on and on.
*鲨鱼妈妈  嘟嘟嘟嘟*
*Mommy shark Doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo*
我再也不想听到鲨鱼  宝宝  或嘟嘟这些词了
I don't want to hear a shark or "baby" or "doo" ever again.
*鲨鱼妈妈  嘟嘟嘟嘟*
*Mommy shark Doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo*
马姬  你个叛徒
Marge, you traitor!
*鲨鱼妈妈*
*Mommy shark*
太好上口了
It's so catchy.
*鲨鱼爸爸  嘟嘟嘟嘟*
*Daddy shark, doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo*
搞什么鬼
Oh, what the hell.
*鲨鱼爸爸  嘟嘟嘟嘟*
*Daddy shark, doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo*
*鲨鱼爸爸*
*Daddy shark*
我的葬礼上要放这首歌
Play this at my funeral!
圣诞老人村
兼夏日"打包驯鹿"狩猎场
精灵耳朵
50美分
为什么我们来的低预算公园
Why do the low-budget parks we go to
有这么多白人垃圾
have so many white trash idiots?
天呐  太好喝了
Boy, that's good.
为什么  为什么
Why? Why?
我要排队去看圣诞老人了
Well, I'm getting right in line for Santa.
预计等待八小时
永远地失去了他的位置
等八小时去看一个喝多了的老胖子
Eight hours to see a fat lazy drunk-o?
我来这个公园就是为了远离一个这样的人
I came to this park to get away from one.
抱抱公牛
警告
不许抱
就连光明节这里都这么多人
Even Chanukah Hollow is packed.
光明节
煤油
来看看光明节陀螺赌场吧
Check out the Dreidel Casino.
加油  玩家赢  玩家赢
Come on, gimmel, gimmel, gimmel!
又是玩家输
Ah, shin again!
我还以为这是犹太教里我擅长的一部分
I thought this would be the one part of Judaism I'm good at.
家有土地神穹顶
果不其然
Typical.
这项目又蠢又无聊  是给小孩玩的
The one ride is a stupid, boring kiddie ride.
至少你会玩得开心
At least you get to have fun.
*外面的世界很恐怖*
*It's a scary place in the world outside*
*土地神正盯着你  所以你最好别哭*
*Gnomes are watching you, so you'd best not cry*
*别流露出恐惧  这点我们知道*
*Don't display any fear, this we know*
*对  很明显  我们的眼睛*
*Yes, it's clear, all our eyes*
*都在盯着你*
*Are watching you*
*外面的世界很恐怖*
*It's a scary place in the world outside*
*土地神正盯着你  所以你最好别哭*
*Gnomes are watching you, so you'd best not cry*
*别流露出恐惧  这点我们知道*
*Don't display any fear, this we know*
*对  很明显*
*Yes, it's clear*
*我们的眼睛都在盯着你*
*All our eyes are watching you*
圣诞老人村
家有土地神穹顶
哥们  谢谢你帮我占了个位子
Hey, buddy, thanks for saving me a spot.
巴仔  你插了那些恶霸的队
Bart, you cut the bullies.
在这种情况下  我们对插队者
In this situation, we assign equal blame
和被插队者加以同等的指责
to the cutter and the cuttee.
放他一马吧  我不想让我的圣诞毛衣沾上血
Let him go. I don't want to get blood on my Christmas sweater.
好吧  你的圣诞毛衣会沾上血的
Oh, there's gonna be blood on your sweater, all right.
我刚说了我不想那样
I just said I didn't want that!
仅限演职人员
侏儒入口
圣诞老人处
卷趾器
仅限演职人员
你好  小伙子
Hello, young man.
上来吧
Climb right up.
圣诞老人  我是巴托罗缪·辛普森
Santa? Bartholomew Simpson.
-你不认识我  不过  -我认识你
- You don't know me, but... - Oh, but I do.
你好呀  巴仔
Hello-ho-ho, Bart.
戏子鲍勃
Sideshow Bob!
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
圣诞老人城堡
他心情很好
He's in a good mood.
太好了  今年我能得到猴子了
Yes. This is the year I get the monkey.
我一直在跟你说
I keep telling you,
猴子意味着重大的责任
a monkey is a huge responsibility.
我在养孩子  我觉得我能养得了猴子
I'm raising a kid. I think I can raise a monkey.
圣诞老人村
兼夏日"打包驯鹿"狩猎场
简直手到擒来  过了这么多年
So easy. After all these years,
我终于能看到生命从你的眼中流逝  你的
I get to watch the life drain from your eye, your I...
我下不了手杀你
I can't kill you!
-想知道为什么吗  -不了
- Want to know why? - Mm, nah.
我是个训练有素的演技派演员
I am a trained method actor.
我入戏太深了
I inhabit my roles.
就像《魅影缝匠》里的丹尼尔·戴-刘易斯
Like Daniel Day-Lewis in Phantom Thread.
或是《爱情导师》里的麦克·梅尔斯那样
Or Mike Myers in The Love Guru.
我为什么要相信你
Why should I trust you?
因为我完全无法脱离角色
Because I am utterly incapable of stepping out of character.
我就是圣诞老人
I am Santa Claus.
就是快乐的老精灵本灵
The jolly old elf himself.
那我们能进去看你了吗
So can we get in to see you?
休息十五分钟  圣诞老人在准备礼物
15-minute break. Santa's making presents.
圣诞老人城堡
请稍等  我们在对圣诞老人进行神圣性背调
警卫
我告诉你们  这人是戏子鲍勃
I'm telling you, this is Sideshow Bob!
-他差点杀了我  -那么
- He tried to kill me! - Well?
我是持证上岗的节日圣诞老人
I am a card-carrying seasonal Santa.
圣诞老人联盟  地区编码5732
Kris Kringle Union, Local 5732.
我也是商场圣诞老人
Hey, I was a mall Santa, too.
我还系着腰带呢
I still wear the belt.
如果你们想花时间和圣诞老人待在一起
If you're gonna spend this much time with our Santa,
你们需要摆好姿势照个相
you have to pose for a photo.
和圣诞老人合影四十美元
Photos with Santa, $40.
马姬  拿你的手机给我拍一张
Marge, just take one with your phone!
-拍到了  -跑
- Got it. - Run!
这能阻止偷我包裹的那些混蛋
This will stop the jerks who've been stealing packages off my porch,
火药
一个带有染色标记的爆炸诱饵
a decoy with an exploding dye marker inside.
你不觉得里面装的火药有点多吗
You don't think you packed in a little too much gunpowder?
别担心  我从残废叔叔那里学到的
Relax. I learned how to do this from my Uncle Two Fingers.
我的天  你就是包裹大盗
Oh, my God. You're the package thief?
莱尼  这是谁干的  你能说话吗
Lenny. Who did this to you? Can you say it?
你能小声说吗
Can you whisper it?
你能用血写出来吗
Can you write it with your blood?
戏子鲍勃
宝宝圣诞节倒计时
我们的圣诞节包裹还没到我有点担心
I'm a little worried our Christmas packages haven't arrived.
马姬  放松  时间很充裕
Marge, relax. There's plenty of time.
现在是晚上八点  平安夜到了
It's 8:00 P.M. Christmas Eve!
坐下来看看福克斯新闻的圣诞节目吧
Just sit back and watch this Fox News yule log.
人权宣言  美国宪法
举全村之力  希拉里著  波斯特的礼仪之书  物种起源  寂静的春天
我们暂停圣诞节目插播一条特别报道
We interrupt this yule log with a special report.
圣诞节礼物的幽灵
春田镇的包裹盗窃事件仍在继续
Package delivery thefts continue in Springfield.
本地居民莱昂纳德·莱尼·莱昂纳德
Local man Leonard "Lenny" Leonard
其包裹的爆炸声打破了圣诞节的氛围
had his jingle bell rung in a package deal gone boom.
我们唯一的线索就是尸体旁边的缩写
Our only clue is these initials next to the corpse.
他不是尸体  还喘气呢
He's not a corpse. He's breathing.
我说是尸体他就是
I say he's a corpse.
我说我不是
And I say I'm not.
你没有权利做决定
you don't get a vote.
缩写指的是戏子鲍勃
"S.B." is Sideshow Bob!
这就是他的目标
That's what he's up to.
他在偷走圣诞节
He's stealing Christmas!
一个圣诞老人不会偷走圣诞节
A fellow Santa could not steal Christmas.
我知道这个神秘的缩写是什么
I know who this mysterious "S.B." is.
欢迎来到监狱  塞尔玛·布伟业
Welcome to jail, Selma Bouvier.
告诉斯科特·巴库拉  史蒂夫·鲍尔默
Uh, tell Scott Bakula, Steve Ballmer
还有桑德拉·布洛克他们逃过一劫
and Sandra Bullock they're off the hook.
两个小时前我就应该
I should've been back
回到《海军罪案调查处:新奥尔良》剧组
at NCIS: New Orleans two hours ago.
你为什么不去《时空怪客》剧组呢
Why don't you just Quantum Leap there?
你为什么不学学怎么当警察呢
Why don't you learn how to be a cop, fatso?
我喜欢  像《错误身份》
I loved it! Mistaken identity!
我卖了十张季票给我牢房里的人
I sold ten, ten season tickets to the guys in my cell.
我们做的每件事都很成功  太好了
Everything we do is successful, booyah!
圣诞老人村
请带我去圣诞老人村
Santa's Village, please.
你去那里做什么
What do you want to go there for?
我要拯救圣诞节
I'm saving Christmas.
每年的这个时候所有孩子都想这么做
Every kid thinks they're doing that this time of year.
我告诉你圣诞老人村恐怕已经关闭了
And as for you, Santa's Village is closed, I'm afraid.
如果我想听你的人生故事  我会选择优步
If I wanted your life story, I would've taken an Uber.
这让我无话可说
Well, that shuts me up.
圣诞老人城堡
没弄清戏子鲍勃想干什么  我是不会离开的
I'm not gonna leave till I find out what Bob's up to.
如果一个小时内没有我的消息就报警
If you don't hear from me in one hour, call the police.
我这边也有问题  巴仔
I have my own problems, Bart.
我妈把我爸关门外雪地里挨冻
My mom just locked my dad out in the snow.
他现在一直在敲我窗户
He keeps tapping at my window.
我妈警告我开窗就没礼物
She said if I open it, no presents.
-真没用  -别挂电话啊
- Useless. - Don't hang up.
我的计划
典型的邪恶反派错误
Classic evil villain mistake.
工作到六十七岁后领退休金
跟同龄人约会  学中文  找到生父
人生目标吗
Life goals?!
别嘲笑我啊
Don't pooh-pooh.
你自己说  我该怎么说服自己
Now for God's sake, how can I convince you
不去杀了你
that I am not going to kill you?!
找到偷礼物的人
Find the person who stole the presents.
好吧  首先要澄清我姓名首字母之罪名
Very well. I shall begin by clearing my initials,
去捉那个真"S.B"  最后
catching the true "S.B." and, if I must,
有必要的话  拯救圣诞
save Christmas for everyone.
我现在开车带你回家
Now let me drive you home.
你想让我坐你车  好吧
You want me to ride with you? Fine.
霰弹枪
Shotgun!
也有副驾驶的意思
出发
Let's roll.
坐副驾驶要掏过路费
Shotgun means you pay the tolls.
我是来拯救圣诞的  计划是这样
So I'm here to save Christmas, and here's my plan.
首先我藏进这个盒子
First, I conceal myself within this box.
你从哪学的这手
Where'd you learn how to do that?
坐小丑车横越全国  你也能学好几手
When you ride cross-country in a clown car, you learn a lot.
想不到
Who knew?
-太棒了  -难以置信
- Brava! - Who knew?
谢谢你们
Thank you.
侯默  现在把我轻放在门廊上
Now, Homer, gently place me on the porch,
他们偷走我后  跟去他们的老巢
and when they steal me, follow them to their lair.
没问题
Will do.
还差点
And...
祝成功
Godspeed.
他们马上就会来
They'll be here any minute.
达夫啤酒
喘不上气
Can't breathe.
氧气
平安夜深夜
*鲨鱼宝宝  嘟嘟嘟嘟*
*Baby shark, doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo*
天啊"S.B."竟然是
Oh, my God, S.B. is
史密瑟斯和伯恩斯
Smithers and Burns!
什么时候要先说史密瑟斯了
Since when does Smithers go first?
你们被拆穿了
The jig is up!
然后  我腿麻
Also, leg cramp.
警察马上就到
The police are on their way.
他们会信你们  还是会信一个送给他们
Who will they believe? You or the billionaire
蒙哥马利沃德公司的奶酪的亿万富翁
who just sent them a Montgomery Ward's cheese log?
伯恩斯先生  您为什么要做这些
Mr. Burns, why did you do this?
守财奴基本操作
Ooh, general Scroogeyness.
不  更内在  守财只是外表
No, it's deeper. It's much deeper than that.
我认为伯恩斯先生很沮丧
I think Mr. Burns is depressed.
你真是个有洞察力的好姑娘
Ooh, you're a very perceptive girl.
别再特写了
That's close enough.
我想让所有人都感受到
I just wanted everyone to experience
我曾在圣诞节的心碎
the same Christmas heartbreak that I once did.
无线电城
距离大萧条结束还有五年
金贝儿百货商场
圣诞老人
爸爸  我的好爸爸
Papa, sweet Papa,
我可以坐在圣诞老人的腿上吗
may I sit on Santa's lap?
我不知道
Well, I don't know.
你是说那个免费发玩具
Santa Claus, giving away free toys,
与我的朋友比尔·美泰儿和弗雷德·孩之宝
undercutting my friends,
美泰儿和孩之宝都是美国的玩具公司
抢生意的圣诞老人吗
Bill Mattel and Fred Hasbro.
拜托了
Please?
你的愿望是什么  小伙子
Well, what's on your wish list, little boy?
罗克福德的袜子猴  斯蒂庞克的脚踏车
A Rockford sock monkey, Studebaker pedal car,
还是今年最流行的礼物  一个橙子
or the most popular gift this year, an orange.
我只想要一个妈妈的抱抱
All I want is a hug from my mommy
和爸爸的微笑
and a smile from my daddy.
我敢肯定你的拥抱和微笑
Oh, well I'm sure there's a hug and a smile
都已经在来的路上了
on their way to you right now. Ho, ho, ho.
下一个
Next.
圣诞节你想要什么
What do you want for Christmas?
我想你遵守承诺和我妈妈结婚
I want you to marry my mom like you said you would.
下一个
Next!
十二月
圣诞节当天到了
Christmas day came...
我来送你去寄宿学校了
I'm here to take you to boarding school.
-在圣诞节吗  -今天不堵车
- On Christmas Day? - Hey, no traffic.
我再次见到父母的时候
The next time I saw my parents,
他们已经笑不出来了
they weren't in a smiling mood.
来晚了
Too late!
除了一亿美元  你们俩什么都没给我
You two never gave me anything except $100 million.
圣诞老人撒谎
Santa lied.
老蒙  你误会我了
But, Monty, you misunderstood me.
圣诞老人  这不可能
Santa? It can't be.
老蒙  现在是1935年
Monty, it's 1935,
我们正在金贝儿百货商场里
and this is Gimbels Department Store,
橱窗里有玩具小火车
with the toy train in the window
电梯工马克西在尽职工作
and Maxie the elevator man.
你在看女式内衣柜台
You're looking at the lingerie department.
试衣间  女式内衣柜台
尽管看  没关系
You can look. It's okay.
对对对  我又是个孩子了
Yes. Yes. Yes! I am a child again.
事实真相是  你的父母很爱你
And the truth is, your parents did love you,
但不是以亲亲抱抱的方式  而是更好的方法
not with hugs and kisses, but with something better--
他们让你成长为一个坚强的人
they made you strong.
你们那个年代的其他大亨们都怎么样了
Where are all the other tycoons from your day?
破产了  死了  被指控性侵
Broke, dead, a lot of #MeToo.
你是全城最富有  最冷血的人
But you're the richest, most ruthless man in town,
都归功于你父母深沉的爱
thanks to your parents' love.
你说得对
It's true.
史密瑟斯  今天是圣诞节
Smithers, it's Christmas,
是你的工作日  快来帮我
which is a work day for you, so help me out.
还是我的生日
And it's my birthday.
两份礼物是不可能的
Don't expect two presents.
我的葡萄干到了
My raisins came!
至少他在吃东西了
Well, at least he's eating.
伯恩斯先生万岁
Huzzah for Mr. Burns!
上帝保佑我们所有人
God bless us, every one.
圣诞节
说真的  这个太棒了
Seriously, this is, this is really nice.
圣诞节  早上六点
我们做到了
We did it.
所有的礼物都放在圣诞树下了
Got all the presents under the tree.
我很幸运  因为没人能偷走我的礼物
I'm lucky because no one could possibly steal my gift.
我的圣诞礼物是抱着我的妻子
All I want is one peaceful moment
享受这宁静的时刻
to hold my wife in my arms.
圣诞节到啦
It's Christmas!
这么早就醒了
Awake already?
-滑动哨  -卡祖笛
- Slide whistle. - Kazoo!
去地下室等我
Meet me in the basement.
好的
Okay.
来张全家福
Picture time.
辛普森一家祝大家圣诞快乐
珍妮  你还没有学会这首曲子吗
Janey, haven't you learned that silly tune yet?
你一遍一遍的弹了这么久  快别练了
You play it over and over again. Now stop it, stop it!
这姑娘确实弹钢琴不太行
That girl is pretty bad at the piano.
你好  卡珊德拉
Hello, Cassandra.
这是我送你的圣诞礼物
I brought you a Christmas present.
我知道你是谁  也知道你做过什么
I know who you are, and I know what you've done,
现在我要你吻我
and I want you to kiss me.
*你真的该走了*
*You really should go*
*外面零下二十度*
*It's 20 below*
*你不能待在这*
*I can't have you here*
*让我喝杯啤酒就好*
*Just get me a beer*
*我已经很绅士了*
*I'm being a gent*
*我允许你吻我*
*I'm giving consent*
*你很有吸引力*
*You are quite inviting*
*那签个字吧*
*I will put it in writing*
亲热合同
*宝贝  外面天寒地冻*
*Baby, it's cold outside*
谁能把灯打开吗
Yarr. Will someone turn on the damn light?!
现在开有点晚了  你觉得呢
A little late, don't you think?
该死
Yarr!
春田机场
阿壳汉堡
史蒂夫  等会  等一下
Steve. Psst. Steve. Wait.
抱歉  我正要离开你们这迷人的小镇
Sorry, I'm just about ready to leave your wonderful town.
这里太棒了  真的很好玩
Great place. Fantastic!
是我去过的最棒的春田镇
The best Springfield I've ever been in. Whoo!
你能教我怎么做这个吗
Can you teach me to do that?
做什么  我天生就是这样
Do what? This is just me.
《救命  我的老板有毒还有辐射》
这咖啡真棒  马上送一卡车到西雅图
Fantastic coffee! Send a truckful to Seattle.
你是怎么保持如此快乐的
How can you possibly be so happy?
你的心中也充满了快乐
It's in you too!
我可不这么认为
I really don't think so.
老蒙  看着我的眼睛
Monty, look me in the eye!
我做不到
I don't know if I can.
你是一条鲜活的生命
You're amazingly alive.
你真是有钱到没朋友
You're rich beyond any sense of justice.
你就是查·蒙哥马利·伯恩斯啊
you're C. Montgomery Burns.
落地时候伤到自己了吧
Hurt yourself on the landing, huh?
不  是起跳的时候
No. On the way up.
用巴仔的肠子装饰大厅
老蒙野外烧烤纸币
阿壳式圣诞快乐
以及天啊  又输了吗
奥·坦能·鲍勃
这个圣诞节
想念鼓手少年
三位智者祝您圣诞快乐
你跟我想喝的一样吗
小挠肚子有个洞
圣诞节的老侯主妇
2020新年快乐喝不停